Guide to the Records of the Institute of African American Affairs RG.9.8
New York University Archives
- Series II: Association for Education in Journalism (AEJ), 61188
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1989; 61229 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1989; 61228 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1989; 61227 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Finalists/Interns: Kalena Hammock, 1989; 61226 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Finalists/Interns: Natasha M. Labaze, AEJMC Applicant, 1989; 61225 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Finalists/Interns: Michael Edwin Watson, AEJMC Applicant, 1989; 61224 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Finalists/Interns: Towanda Underdue, AEJMC, 1989; 61223 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1990; 61222 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1990; 61221 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1990; 61220 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1990; 61219 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Kimetris Baltrip, 1990; 61218 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226031 8
  - AEJMC Applicant: Efrem Keir Graham, 1990; 61217 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Tanya Haughton, 1990; 61216 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Elizabeth R. Mesa, 1990; 61215 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Tara Roberts, 1990; 61214 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Andrea Wiggins, 1990; 61213 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Lisa Chin, 1990; 61212 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Cheryl Hendricks, 1990; 61211 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Sirena Huang, 1990; 61210 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Kimberly Maxwell, 1990; 61209 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Raoul Mowatt, 1990; 61208 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Teresa C. Puente, 1990; 61207 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Dara N. Shariff, 1990; 61206 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Towanda Underdue, 1990; 61205 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - AEJMC Applicant: Valentina Wilson, 1990; 61204 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1991; 61203 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1991; 61202 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1991; 61201 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Geraldine Alumit, AEJ, 1991; 61200 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Marisol Bello, AEJ, 1991; 61199 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Melinda A. Bond, 1991; 61198 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Stacy Coates, AEJ, 1991; 61197 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Alicia Coulote, AEJ, 1991; 61196 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Cora Daniels, AEJ, 1991; 61195 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Heidi W. Durrow, 1991; 61194 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Patricia Edwards, 1991; 61193 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Grace Kyungwon Hong, AEJ, 1991; 61192 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Sophia V. McGregor, AEJ, 1991; 61191 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Kimberly R. Riley, AEJ, 1991; 61190 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Jennifer Rodriguez, AEJ, 1991; 61189 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Series III: Earl S. Davis Correspondence, 60498
  - ABFA, 1990; 61187 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - ABFA - Confidential For Adm. Report, 1990; 61186 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - M.L.King, Jan 15, 1987; 61185 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - African Materials, Nov 1990; 61184 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - African Global Heritage Assoc., Dec 17, 1990; 61183 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - AMC - Colleagues Grp., May 8, 1986; 61182 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226032 6
  - Assoc. Black Women in Higher Education, Jun 4, 1905; 61181 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Black Alumni - Call in list, undated; 61180 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Black Creation, undated; 61179 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Black Student Center, undated; 61178 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Black Family Conference, undated; 61177 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Untitled [approximately 2 linear inches of unfoldered materials (IAAA personnel information, correspondence, articles, flyers, etc.); folder provided], undated; 61176 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Untitled [includes material on African Panorama, correspondence, and articles], undated; 61175 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Events, 1983; 61174 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Resource Network, 1991; 61173 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Dr. Elizabeth Henshaw, Visiting Professorship - Exchange, Dec 3, 1985; 61172 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Elizabeth Henshaw - Nigeria [EMPTY], undated; 61171 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Franco, undated; 61170 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Hutchins, Annette, Oct 16, 1986; 61169 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - IAAA Advisory Minutes, undated; 61168 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - IAAA History, undated; 61167 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - IAAA Annual Reports, undated; 61166 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Orde Coombs Collection, undated; 61165 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226033 4
  - Rod Rogers Dance Company, Mar 29, 1984; 61164 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Soul of Reason - Interview Questions, Feb. 1978- Nov 1978; 61163 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Soul of Reason - Interview Questions, Nov 1978-Jul 1979; 61162 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Untitled [approximately 1 lin. inch of unfoldered material (NYU Purchasing; correspondence; "The Black Woman and the Bicentennial Conference, June 24-27, 1976," packet and notes); folder provided], 61161 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - [Non-NYU Publications], undated; 61160 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Six Annual Community Service Award and Tribute, Jun 21, 1991; 61159 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Resource Network's Day Tour of Harlem, Jun 22, 1991; 61158 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Lecture: "African History: An African Perspective" by Dr. Albert Adu Boahem, Oct 9, 1991; 61157 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Lecture/Reception: "Strengthening the Bond Between People of African Heritage", Oct 14, 1991; 61156 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - ABFAS Open House Reception, Oct 16, 1991; 61155 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Lecture: "Forging Connections: African American/African Caribbean", Nov 13, 1991; 61154 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - The NYC 1992 Media Conference: "Accessing the Media in NYC"(3 folders), Feb 5, 1992; 61153 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Tisch S.O.A. Black and Hispanic Film Festival(3 folders), Feb 18, 1992-Feb 25, 1992; 61152 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Annual Choral Celebration of Black History-NYU All University Gospel Choir, Feb 20, 1992; 61151 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Black History Month Celebration at the Bedford Stuyvesant Community Mental Health Center, Inc. Keynote: Earl Davis, Feb 25, 1992; 61150 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Lecture/Reception: "An Evening With The Elders", Feb 27, 1992; 61149 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - "Women As a Catalyst For Social Change" Lecture by Mrs. Coretta Scott King, Mar 9, 1992; 61148 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - NYU Black Lobby Day trip to Albany, Mar 17, 1992; 61147 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226034 2
  - NYU Black Lobby Day trip to Albany, Mar 17, 1992; 61146 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - NYU Black Lobby Day trip to Albany, Mar 17, 1992; 61145 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - NYU Black Lobby Day trip to Albany, Mar 17, 1992; 61144 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - The 54th Massachusetts Colored Infantry Lecture by Jacqueline Shearer and Professor Thelma Foote, Apr 23, 1992; 61143 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Black and Latino Awards Ceremony, May 2, 1992; 61142 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Welcome Reception for Dr. Manthia Diawara, Sep 18, 1992; 61141 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - The Coalition for Columbus on Trial; "500 Years of Cultural Resistance" and a Prayer March to the Negro Burial Site, Oct 1, 1992; 61140 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - The 1992 Christopher Columbus Consortium, NY Presents COLVMBVS RECONCILIATION FORVM: "THE WELL BEING IN THE XXIrst CENTURY.", Oct 9, 1992-Oct 11, 1992; 61139 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Christopher Columbus Consortium: Dr. Sandra Dernini, Jan 1992; 61138 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992; 61137 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992; 61136 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992; 61135 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992; 61134 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992; 61133 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226035 9
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992; 61132 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992; 61131 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Conference: Black Theatre in America, 1992 "Renaissance Revival", Oct 23, 1992-Oct 25, 1992; 61130 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - "The Herencia Latina" November Celebration-Concert at Loeb Center: featuring Willie Colon and His Legal Alien Band, Nov 6, 1992; 61129 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Movie: "Passin It on" -- A Documentary Film About Dhoruba Bin Wahad and the Black Panther Part, Dec 5, 1992; 61128 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - James Weldon Johnson, Nov 12, 1990; 61127 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Nigerian National Culture Group, Jul 8, 2006; 61126 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - National Conference of Artists, Apr 5, 1994-Apr 11, 1993; 61125 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Black Theater in America, undated; 61124 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - NY Urban Coalition Educational Summit, Dec 12, 1993-Dec 13, 1993; 61123 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Festac Reunion, Apr 11, 1993; 61122 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Black Articles, 1966; 61121 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Black Articles, 1969; 61120 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Black Literary, 1969; 61119 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Conference on African and African American Studies in Atlanta, GA, 1969; 61118 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence of Roscoe Brown, Director-IAAA, 1969; 61117 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226036 7
  - IAAA Alteration of Office, 1969; 61116 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - IAAA Background Information, 1969; 61115 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - IAAA Background Information, 1969; 61114 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - IAAA Background Information, 1969; 61113 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - IAAA Background Information, 1969; 61112 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - IAAA Fundraising, 1969; 61111 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - IAAA Lecture/Seminar Report and Evaluation, 1969; 61110 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - IAAA Organizational Proposal Correspondence, 1969; 61109 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - IAAA Organizational Proposal, 1969; 61108 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - IAAA Progress Report, 1969; 61107 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - IAAA Progress Report, 1969; 61106 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Center Correspondence, 1969; 61105 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Organizational Proposal for an Afro-American Institute at NYU In Honor of the Late Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., 1969; 61104 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Publications-NYU: The Black Student at NYU, 1969; 61103 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - X, Malcolm Research Tape Transcription, 1969; 61102 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - X, Malcolm Research Tape Transcription, 1969; 61101 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - X, Malcolm Research Tape Transcription, 1969; 61100 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - X, Malcolm Research Tape Transcription, 1969; 61099 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - X, Malcolm Research Tape Transcription, 1969; 61098 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - X, Malcolm Research Tape Transcription, 1969; 61097 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1969; 61096 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1969; 61095 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Black Articles, 1969; 61094 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Black Creation Magazine, 1970; 61093 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Black History Book Project, 1970; 61092 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Black History Book Project, 1970; 61091 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Black Studies Coordinating Council, 1970; 61090 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Black Studies Courses, 1970; 61089 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, Roscoe Brown, IAAA Dir., 1970; 61088 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Democratic Republic of the Congo, 1970; 61087 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - IAAA Activities, 1970; 61086 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - IAAA Advisory Board, 1970; 61085 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1970; 61084 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Billings, Charles E., 1970; 61083 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Goines, Dr. Leonard, 1970; 61082 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Kan, Michael, 1970; 61081 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Mitchell, Loften, 1970; 61080 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Young, Joseph, 1970; 61079 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Young, Philip, 1970; 61078 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - IAAA Book Fair, 1970; 61077 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - IAAA Conference Reports, 1970; 61076 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - IAAA Evaluations, 1970; 61075 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - IAAA Fact Sheet, 1970; 61074 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - IAAA Fundraising, 1970; 61073 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - IAAA Fundraising, Benefit Performance, 1st Anniversary- Steve Depass, 1970; 61072 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - IAAA Fundraising, Benefit Performance, 1st Anniversary- Steve Depass, 1970; 61071 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - IAAA Lecture: Alex Haley, 1970; 61070 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - IAAA Progress Report (1), 1970; 61069 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - IAAA Progress Report (2), 1970; 61068 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - IAAA Proposal for Research: IAAA Training Minority Group Research and Evaluation Specialists, 1970; 61067 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226037 5
  - IAAA Publicity, 1970; 61066 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - IAAA Report, Fall Term, 1970; 61065 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - IAAA Staff Bulletin, 1970; 61064 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - IAAA Staff Report, 1970; 61063 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - IAAA Steering Committee, 1970; 61062 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Journal of Negro Education, 1970; 61061 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Center Correspondence, 1970; 61060 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Center Correspondence, 1970; 61059 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Center Publications: "The Niggafied Press" Volumes 3-8, 1970; 61058 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - NYU Publication: Internal for Faculty and Administration, 1970; 61057 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - The New York Urban Coalition (1), 1970; 61056 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - The New York Urban Coalition (2), 1970; 61055 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Proposal for Research, 1970; 61054 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Sojourner Newspaper, Publication of IAAA, 1970; 61053 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Still Here Magazine, 1970; 61052 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1970; 61051 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Black Articles, 1971; 61050 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Black Creation, 1971; 61049 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Black Literary, 1971; 61048 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Black Studies Courses, 1971; 61047 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Black Studies Course Listing, 1971; 61046 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Black Studies Programs in the U.S., 1971; 61045 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Black Studies Speakers, 1971; 61044 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Chancellor's Report, IAAA, 1971; 61043 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence of E. R. Braithwaite, 1971; 61042 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence of E. R. Braithwaite, 1971; 61041 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence of Dr. Roscoe Brown, 1971; 61040 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Directories-Business, Educational (National Periodicals and Journals), 1971; 61039 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - IAAA Activities-Program Planning, 1971; 61038 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee Correspondence, 1971; 61037 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Coombs, Orde, 1971; 61036 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Exum, William, 1971; 61035 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Floyd, Art, 1971; 61034 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Furman, Roger, 1971; 61033 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Garriga, Jose, 1971; 61032 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Grimes, Larry, 1971; 61031 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Hall, Fred, 1971; 61030 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Holmes, Robert, 1971; 61029 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Jenkins, Adelbert, 1971; 61028 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Jordan, John Samuel, 1971; 61027 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Mickens, Al, 1971; 61026 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Ofonogoro, Walter, 1971; 61025 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Thornton, Virginius, 1971; 61024 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - IAAA Black Studies Instructors: Walker, Dr. Wyatt T., 1971; 61023 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - IAAA Fundraising, 1971; 61022 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1971; 61021 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - IAAA Orientation (1), 1971; 61020 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - IAAA Orientation (2), 1971; 61019 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - IAAA Staff, 1971; 61018 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - IMANI Magazine, 1972; 61017 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - IMANI Magazine, 1972; 61016 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - The Institute of the Black World Monthly Report, 1971; 61015 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Center, 1971; 61014 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Kirng, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Scholarships, 1971; 61013 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - M.A. Program in Black Studies, 1971; 61012 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Minority Student Recruitment, 1971; 61011 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226038 3
  - NYU Publication: Internal for Faculty and Administrators, 1971; 61010 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Report to Ford Foundation, IAAA, 1971; 61009 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Exchange Program, 1971; 61008 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1971; 61007 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Agbeli, Godwin-African Dance Class, 1972; 61006 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Art Collection-Grey Art Gallery, 1972; 61005 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Black Articles, 1972; 61004 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Black Creation, 1972; 61003 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Black Creation, 1972; 61002 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Black Films, 1972; 61001 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Black Studies Courses, 1972; 61000 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Black Studies in Higher Education, 1971-1972; 60999 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Dr. Roscoe Brown, 1972; 60998 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Directory - Black Urban Alliances, 1972; 60997 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Final Report to the Ford Foundation, 1972; 60996 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Giovanni, Nikki, Reception, 1972; 60995 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1972; 60994 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - IAAA AEJ Program, 1972; 60993 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - IAAA History/Research, 1972; 60992 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - IAAA History/Research, 1972; 60991 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - IAAA History/Research, 1972; 60990 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1972; 60989 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - IAAA Staff, 1972; 60988 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - IAAA Training Program-Community College Black Studies Instructors, 1972; 60987 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - IAAA Training Program: Junior or Community College Teachers in Black Studies, 1972; 60986 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - The Institute of the Black World Monthly Report, 1972; 60985 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther King Center, 1972; 60984 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Program, 1972; 60983 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - M.A. Program in Black Studies, 1972; 60982 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Mathematical Sciences - List of Departmental Chairpersons, 1972; 60981 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - NYU Publication: Internal for Faculty & Admin., 1972; 60980 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Proposals for Funding of Research Projects, 1972; 60979 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Research Project: Community College, Black Studies Instructors, 1972; 60978 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Sojourner Newspaper, 1972; 60977 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Sojourner Newspaper, 1972; 60976 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Sports Foundation, 1972; 60975 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Washington Square Journal, 1972; 60974 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Wooden's John-Success Project, 1972; 60973 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - IAAA Fundraising, 1972; 60972 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - IAAA Newsletter, 1972; 60971 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Black Creation Magazine, 1973; 60970 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Black Films, 1973; 60969 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Black Literary, 1973; 60968 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Black Studies Courses, Graduate Level, 1973; 60967 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - BSSC (Black Student Service Center) Proposal, 1973; 60966 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence: Dr. Roscoe Brown, 1973; 60965 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Dilemmas of Afro-Americans (IAAA Course) taught by Dr. Eugene Callender, 1973; 60964 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - IAAA Advisory Committee, 1973; 60963 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - IAAA Annual Report (1), 1973; 60962 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - IAAA Annual Report (2), 1973; 60961 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - IAAA Annual Report (3), 1973; 60960 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1973; 60959 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - IAAA Project: Instructional Strategies and the Development of Political Thinking Among Emerging Adolescents, 1973; 60958 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - IAAA Project: Instructional Strategies and the Development of Political Thinking Among Emerging Adolescents, 1973; 60957 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - IAAA Staff Correspondence, 1973; 60956 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - The Institute of the Black World Monthly Report, 1973; 60955 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Journalism Council (Job/Scholarship Referral Bulletin For Minorities), 1973; 60954 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1973; 60953 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Reception, 1973; 60952 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Memorial Program, 1973; 60951 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - NYU Publication: Internal for Faculty and Administrators, 1973; 60950 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - NYU Staff Publication, 1973; 60949 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - The New York Urban Coalition, 1973; 60948 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1974; 60947 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Association of Black Faculty, 1974; 60946 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226039 1
  - BSSC (Black Student Service Center), 1974; 60945 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Black Studies Programs, 1974; 60944 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - IAAA Annual Report, 1974; 60943 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - IAAA Annual Report (2), 1974; 60942 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - IAAA Annual Report (3), 1974; 60941 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - IAAA Annual Report (4), 1974; 60940 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - IAAA Annual Report (draft), 1974; 60939 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - IAAA Informal Seminar Series, 1974; 60938 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - IAAA Mainstream (Radio Production/Show), 1974; 60937 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - IAAA Newsletter "Notes", 1974; 60936 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - IAAA Program Planning, 1974; 60935 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - IAAA Proposal for Evaluation of Title I and Title VII Program, 1974; 60934 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Journalism Council, Inc., 1974; 60933 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Fourth Annual Memorial Services, 1974; 60932 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1974; 60931 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1974; 60930 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Graduate Certificates, 1974; 60929 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Reception for Graduates, 1974; 60928 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther Scholarships/Correspondence, 1974; 60927 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Minority Graduate Student Locater Service, 1974; 60926 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - NYU Report Biweekly/Journal, 1974; 60925 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Robinson, Jackie Management Corp., 1974; 60924 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Walker, Dr. Leroy (NYU Alumnus), 1974; 60923 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Washington Square News, 1974; 60922 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Afro-American and Related Courses at NYU, 1975; 60921 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Black Creation Magazine Copyrights, 1975; 60920 (Box 22, Folder 28)